---
-
    question: "Find 48% of 49"
    solution: "Calculate $0.48 \\times 49$"
    answer: 23.52
-
    question: "Find 8% of 220"
    solution: "Calculate $0.08 \\times 220$"
    answer: 17.6
-
    question: "Find 40% of 233"
    solution: "Calculate $0.4 \\times 233$"
    answer: 93.2
-
    question: "Find 74% of 110"
    solution: "Calculate $0.74 \\times 110$"
    answer: 81.4
-
    question: "Find 21% of 98"
    solution: "Calculate $0.21 \\times 98$"
    answer: 20.58
-
    question: "Find 4% of 159"
    solution: "Calculate $0.04 \\times 159$"
    answer: 6.36
-
    question: "Find 17% of 208"
    solution: "Calculate $0.17 \\times 208$"
    answer: 35.36
-
    question: "Find 50% of 143"
    solution: "Calculate $0.5 \\times 143$"
    answer: 71.5
-
    question: "Find 26% of 152"
    solution: "Calculate $0.26 \\times 152$"
    answer: 39.52
-
    question: "Find 34% of 178"
    solution: "Calculate $0.34 \\times 178$"
    answer: 60.52
-
    question: "Find 12% of 136"
    solution: "Calculate $0.12 \\times 136$"
    answer: 16.32
-
    question: "Find 33% of 220"
    solution: "Calculate $0.33 \\times 220$"
    answer: 72.6
-
    question: "Find 62% of 90"
    solution: "Calculate $0.62 \\times 90$"
    answer: 55.8
-
    question: "Find 6% of 201"
    solution: "Calculate $0.06 \\times 201$"
    answer: 12.06
-
    question: "Find 51% of 69"
    solution: "Calculate $0.51 \\times 69$"
    answer: 35.19
-
    question: "Find 42% of 227"
    solution: "Calculate $0.42 \\times 227$"
    answer: 95.34
-
    question: "Find 30% of 37"
    solution: "Calculate $0.3 \\times 37$"
    answer: 11.1
-
    question: "Find 16% of 175"
    solution: "Calculate $0.16 \\times 175$"
    answer: 28
-
    question: "Find 80% of 66"
    solution: "Calculate $0.8 \\times 66$"
    answer: 52.8
-
    question: "Find 48% of 206"
    solution: "Calculate $0.48 \\times 206$"
    answer: 98.88
-
    question: "Find 28% of 159"
    solution: "Calculate $0.28 \\times 159$"
    answer: 44.52
-
    question: "Find 79% of 162"
    solution: "Calculate $0.79 \\times 162$"
    answer: 127.98
-
    question: "Find 40% of 192"
    solution: "Calculate $0.4 \\times 192$"
    answer: 76.8
-
    question: "Find 49% of 62"
    solution: "Calculate $0.49 \\times 62$"
    answer: 30.38
-
    question: "Find 80% of 189"
    solution: "Calculate $0.8 \\times 189$"
    answer: 151.2
-
    question: "Find 25% of 185"
    solution: "Calculate $0.25 \\times 185$"
    answer: 46.25
-
    question: "Find 28% of 217"
    solution: "Calculate $0.28 \\times 217$"
    answer: 60.76
-
    question: "Find 38% of 53"
    solution: "Calculate $0.38 \\times 53$"
    answer: 20.14
-
    question: "Find 38% of 31"
    solution: "Calculate $0.38 \\times 31$"
    answer: 11.78
-
    question: "Find 14% of 136"
    solution: "Calculate $0.14 \\times 136$"
    answer: 19.04
-
    question: "Find 48% of 201"
    solution: "Calculate $0.48 \\times 201$"
    answer: 96.48
-
    question: "Find 51% of 224"
    solution: "Calculate $0.51 \\times 224$"
    answer: 114.24
-
    question: "Find 90% of 129"
    solution: "Calculate $0.9 \\times 129$"
    answer: 116.1
-
    question: "Find 43% of 243"
    solution: "Calculate $0.43 \\times 243$"
    answer: 104.49
-
    question: "Find 65% of 112"
    solution: "Calculate $0.65 \\times 112$"
    answer: 72.8
-
    question: "Find 59% of 246"
    solution: "Calculate $0.59 \\times 246$"
    answer: 145.14
-
    question: "Find 75% of 223"
    solution: "Calculate $0.75 \\times 223$"
    answer: 167.25
-
    question: "Find 62% of 216"
    solution: "Calculate $0.62 \\times 216$"
    answer: 133.92
-
    question: "Find 65% of 93"
    solution: "Calculate $0.65 \\times 93$"
    answer: 60.45
-
    question: "Find 68% of 232"
    solution: "Calculate $0.68 \\times 232$"
    answer: 157.76
-
    question: "Find 39% of 145"
    solution: "Calculate $0.39 \\times 145$"
    answer: 56.55
-
    question: "Find 60% of 226"
    solution: "Calculate $0.6 \\times 226$"
    answer: 135.6
-
    question: "Find 72% of 238"
    solution: "Calculate $0.72 \\times 238$"
    answer: 171.36
-
    question: "Find 5% of 233"
    solution: "Calculate $0.05 \\times 233$"
    answer: 11.65
-
    question: "Find 10% of 43"
    solution: "Calculate $0.1 \\times 43$"
    answer: 4.3
-
    question: "Find 52% of 93"
    solution: "Calculate $0.52 \\times 93$"
    answer: 48.36
-
    question: "Find 72% of 179"
    solution: "Calculate $0.72 \\times 179$"
    answer: 128.88
-
    question: "Find 44% of 73"
    solution: "Calculate $0.44 \\times 73$"
    answer: 32.12
-
    question: "Find 31% of 108"
    solution: "Calculate $0.31 \\times 108$"
    answer: 33.48
-
    question: "Find 34% of 66"
    solution: "Calculate $0.34 \\times 66$"
    answer: 22.44
-
    question: "Find 40% of 92"
    solution: "Calculate $0.4 \\times 92$"
    answer: 36.8
-
    question: "Find 45% of 83"
    solution: "Calculate $0.45 \\times 83$"
    answer: 37.35
-
    question: "Find 24% of 31"
    solution: "Calculate $0.24 \\times 31$"
    answer: 7.44
-
    question: "Find 33% of 89"
    solution: "Calculate $0.33 \\times 89$"
    answer: 29.37
-
    question: "Find 77% of 213"
    solution: "Calculate $0.77 \\times 213$"
    answer: 164.01
-
    question: "Find 64% of 98"
    solution: "Calculate $0.64 \\times 98$"
    answer: 62.72
-
    question: "Find 61% of 202"
    solution: "Calculate $0.61 \\times 202$"
    answer: 123.22
-
    question: "Find 49% of 178"
    solution: "Calculate $0.49 \\times 178$"
    answer: 87.22
-
    question: "Find 50% of 84"
    solution: "Calculate $0.5 \\times 84$"
    answer: 42
-
    question: "Find 57% of 158"
    solution: "Calculate $0.57 \\times 158$"
    answer: 90.06
-
    question: "Find 46% of 229"
    solution: "Calculate $0.46 \\times 229$"
    answer: 105.34
-
    question: "Find 69% of 147"
    solution: "Calculate $0.69 \\times 147$"
    answer: 101.43
-
    question: "Find 34% of 128"
    solution: "Calculate $0.34 \\times 128$"
    answer: 43.52
-
    question: "Find 18% of 89"
    solution: "Calculate $0.18 \\times 89$"
    answer: 16.02
-
    question: "Find 72% of 90"
    solution: "Calculate $0.72 \\times 90$"
    answer: 64.8
-
    question: "Find 10% of 240"
    solution: "Calculate $0.1 \\times 240$"
    answer: 24
-
    question: "Find 22% of 187"
    solution: "Calculate $0.22 \\times 187$"
    answer: 41.14
-
    question: "Find 29% of 44"
    solution: "Calculate $0.29 \\times 44$"
    answer: 12.76
-
    question: "Find 45% of 193"
    solution: "Calculate $0.45 \\times 193$"
    answer: 86.85
-
    question: "Find 62% of 172"
    solution: "Calculate $0.62 \\times 172$"
    answer: 106.64
-
    question: "Find 17% of 212"
    solution: "Calculate $0.17 \\times 212$"
    answer: 36.04
-
    question: "Find 8% of 233"
    solution: "Calculate $0.08 \\times 233$"
    answer: 18.64
-
    question: "Find 81% of 124"
    solution: "Calculate $0.81 \\times 124$"
    answer: 100.44
-
    question: "Find 70% of 200"
    solution: "Calculate $0.7 \\times 200$"
    answer: 140
-
    question: "Find 51% of 100"
    solution: "Calculate $0.51 \\times 100$"
    answer: 51
-
    question: "Find 83% of 134"
    solution: "Calculate $0.83 \\times 134$"
    answer: 111.22
-
    question: "Find 29% of 41"
    solution: "Calculate $0.29 \\times 41$"
    answer: 11.89
-
    question: "Find 58% of 114"
    solution: "Calculate $0.58 \\times 114$"
    answer: 66.12
-
    question: "Find 61% of 113"
    solution: "Calculate $0.61 \\times 113$"
    answer: 68.93
-
    question: "Find 20% of 143"
    solution: "Calculate $0.2 \\times 143$"
    answer: 28.6
-
    question: "Find 8% of 221"
    solution: "Calculate $0.08 \\times 221$"
    answer: 17.68
-
    question: "Find 26% of 142"
    solution: "Calculate $0.26 \\times 142$"
    answer: 36.92
-
    question: "Find 49% of 140"
    solution: "Calculate $0.49 \\times 140$"
    answer: 68.6
-
    question: "Find 46% of 208"
    solution: "Calculate $0.46 \\times 208$"
    answer: 95.68
-
    question: "Find 59% of 105"
    solution: "Calculate $0.59 \\times 105$"
    answer: 61.95
-
    question: "Find 34% of 92"
    solution: "Calculate $0.34 \\times 92$"
    answer: 31.28
-
    question: "Find 36% of 106"
    solution: "Calculate $0.36 \\times 106$"
    answer: 38.16
-
    question: "Find 27% of 178"
    solution: "Calculate $0.27 \\times 178$"
    answer: 48.06
-
    question: "Find 38% of 143"
    solution: "Calculate $0.38 \\times 143$"
    answer: 54.34
-
    question: "Find 36% of 112"
    solution: "Calculate $0.36 \\times 112$"
    answer: 40.32
-
    question: "Find 74% of 143"
    solution: "Calculate $0.74 \\times 143$"
    answer: 105.82
-
    question: "Find 74% of 145"
    solution: "Calculate $0.74 \\times 145$"
    answer: 107.3
-
    question: "Find 72% of 22"
    solution: "Calculate $0.72 \\times 22$"
    answer: 15.84
-
    question: "Find 88% of 212"
    solution: "Calculate $0.88 \\times 212$"
    answer: 186.56
-
    question: "Find 62% of 46"
    solution: "Calculate $0.62 \\times 46$"
    answer: 28.52
-
    question: "Find 66% of 45"
    solution: "Calculate $0.66 \\times 45$"
    answer: 29.7
-
    question: "Find 6% of 57"
    solution: "Calculate $0.06 \\times 57$"
    answer: 3.42
-
    question: "Find 65% of 51"
    solution: "Calculate $0.65 \\times 51$"
    answer: 33.15
-
    question: "Find 62% of 117"
    solution: "Calculate $0.62 \\times 117$"
    answer: 72.54
-
    question: "Find 50% of 225"
    solution: "Calculate $0.5 \\times 225$"
    answer: 112.5
-
    question: "Increase 52 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 52$ and then add on, or Find 140% of 52, $1.4 \\times 52$"
    answer: 72.8
-
    question: "Increase 224 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 224$ and then add on, or Find 180% of 224, $1.8 \\times 224$"
    answer: 403.2
-
    question: "Increase 153 by 10%"
    solution: "Find 10% $0.1 \\times 153$ and then add on, or Find 110% of 153, $1.1 \\times 153$"
    answer: 168.3
-
    question: "Increase 56 by 75%"
    solution: "Find 75% $0.75 \\times 56$ and then add on, or Find 175% of 56, $1.75 \\times 56$"
    answer: 98
-
    question: "Increase 16 by 75%"
    solution: "Find 75% $0.75 \\times 16$ and then add on, or Find 175% of 16, $1.75 \\times 16$"
    answer: 28
-
    question: "Increase 207 by 90%"
    solution: "Find 90% $0.9 \\times 207$ and then add on, or Find 190% of 207, $1.9 \\times 207$"
    answer: 393.3
-
    question: "Increase 162 by 60%"
    solution: "Find 60% $0.6 \\times 162$ and then add on, or Find 160% of 162, $1.6 \\times 162$"
    answer: 259.2
-
    question: "Increase 220 by 65%"
    solution: "Find 65% $0.65 \\times 220$ and then add on, or Find 165% of 220, $1.65 \\times 220$"
    answer: 363
-
    question: "Increase 113 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 113$ and then add on, or Find 140% of 113, $1.4 \\times 113$"
    answer: 158.2
-
    question: "Increase 123 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 123$ and then add on, or Find 135% of 123, $1.35 \\times 123$"
    answer: 166.05
-
    question: "Increase 185 by 50%"
    solution: "Find 50% $0.5 \\times 185$ and then add on, or Find 150% of 185, $1.5 \\times 185$"
    answer: 277.5
-
    question: "Increase 242 by 55%"
    solution: "Find 55% $0.55 \\times 242$ and then add on, or Find 155% of 242, $1.55 \\times 242$"
    answer: 375.1
-
    question: "Increase 47 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 47$ and then add on, or Find 135% of 47, $1.35 \\times 47$"
    answer: 63.45
-
    question: "Increase 110 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 110$ and then add on, or Find 105% of 110, $1.05 \\times 110$"
    answer: 115.5
-
    question: "Increase 161 by 75%"
    solution: "Find 75% $0.75 \\times 161$ and then add on, or Find 175% of 161, $1.75 \\times 161$"
    answer: 281.75
-
    question: "Increase 228 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 228$ and then add on, or Find 130% of 228, $1.3 \\times 228$"
    answer: 296.4
-
    question: "Increase 220 by 15%"
    solution: "Find 15% $0.15 \\times 220$ and then add on, or Find 115% of 220, $1.15 \\times 220$"
    answer: 253
-
    question: "Increase 36 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 36$ and then add on, or Find 105% of 36, $1.05 \\times 36$"
    answer: 37.8
-
    question: "Increase 233 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 233$ and then add on, or Find 105% of 233, $1.05 \\times 233$"
    answer: 244.65
-
    question: "Increase 227 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 227$ and then add on, or Find 135% of 227, $1.35 \\times 227$"
    answer: 306.45
-
    question: "Increase 215 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 215$ and then add on, or Find 180% of 215, $1.8 \\times 215$"
    answer: 387
-
    question: "Increase 235 by 10%"
    solution: "Find 10% $0.1 \\times 235$ and then add on, or Find 110% of 235, $1.1 \\times 235$"
    answer: 258.5
-
    question: "Increase 234 by 15%"
    solution: "Find 15% $0.15 \\times 234$ and then add on, or Find 115% of 234, $1.15 \\times 234$"
    answer: 269.1
-
    question: "Increase 78 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 78$ and then add on, or Find 130% of 78, $1.3 \\times 78$"
    answer: 101.4
-
    question: "Increase 222 by 70%"
    solution: "Find 70% $0.7 \\times 222$ and then add on, or Find 170% of 222, $1.7 \\times 222$"
    answer: 377.4
-
    question: "Increase 142 by 25%"
    solution: "Find 25% $0.25 \\times 142$ and then add on, or Find 125% of 142, $1.25 \\times 142$"
    answer: 177.5
-
    question: "Increase 231 by 85%"
    solution: "Find 85% $0.85 \\times 231$ and then add on, or Find 185% of 231, $1.85 \\times 231$"
    answer: 427.35
-
    question: "Increase 63 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 63$ and then add on, or Find 105% of 63, $1.05 \\times 63$"
    answer: 66.15
-
    question: "Increase 248 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 248$ and then add on, or Find 140% of 248, $1.4 \\times 248$"
    answer: 347.2
-
    question: "Increase 196 by 65%"
    solution: "Find 65% $0.65 \\times 196$ and then add on, or Find 165% of 196, $1.65 \\times 196$"
    answer: 323.4
-
    question: "Increase 238 by 55%"
    solution: "Find 55% $0.55 \\times 238$ and then add on, or Find 155% of 238, $1.55 \\times 238$"
    answer: 368.9
-
    question: "Increase 241 by 45%"
    solution: "Find 45% $0.45 \\times 241$ and then add on, or Find 145% of 241, $1.45 \\times 241$"
    answer: 349.45
-
    question: "Increase 245 by 25%"
    solution: "Find 25% $0.25 \\times 245$ and then add on, or Find 125% of 245, $1.25 \\times 245$"
    answer: 306.25
-
    question: "Increase 237 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 237$ and then add on, or Find 180% of 237, $1.8 \\times 237$"
    answer: 426.6
-
    question: "Increase 108 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 108$ and then add on, or Find 180% of 108, $1.8 \\times 108$"
    answer: 194.4
-
    question: "Increase 112 by 20%"
    solution: "Find 20% $0.2 \\times 112$ and then add on, or Find 120% of 112, $1.2 \\times 112$"
    answer: 134.4
-
    question: "Increase 94 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 94$ and then add on, or Find 140% of 94, $1.4 \\times 94$"
    answer: 131.6
-
    question: "Increase 164 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 164$ and then add on, or Find 180% of 164, $1.8 \\times 164$"
    answer: 295.2
-
    question: "Increase 204 by 70%"
    solution: "Find 70% $0.7 \\times 204$ and then add on, or Find 170% of 204, $1.7 \\times 204$"
    answer: 346.8
-
    question: "Increase 154 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 154$ and then add on, or Find 105% of 154, $1.05 \\times 154$"
    answer: 161.7
-
    question: "Increase 82 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 82$ and then add on, or Find 130% of 82, $1.3 \\times 82$"
    answer: 106.6
-
    question: "Increase 102 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 102$ and then add on, or Find 180% of 102, $1.8 \\times 102$"
    answer: 183.6
-
    question: "Increase 30 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 30$ and then add on, or Find 130% of 30, $1.3 \\times 30$"
    answer: 39
-
    question: "Increase 47 by 65%"
    solution: "Find 65% $0.65 \\times 47$ and then add on, or Find 165% of 47, $1.65 \\times 47$"
    answer: 77.55
-
    question: "Increase 199 by 10%"
    solution: "Find 10% $0.1 \\times 199$ and then add on, or Find 110% of 199, $1.1 \\times 199$"
    answer: 218.9
-
    question: "Increase 181 by 60%"
    solution: "Find 60% $0.6 \\times 181$ and then add on, or Find 160% of 181, $1.6 \\times 181$"
    answer: 289.6
-
    question: "Increase 199 by 85%"
    solution: "Find 85% $0.85 \\times 199$ and then add on, or Find 185% of 199, $1.85 \\times 199$"
    answer: 368.15
-
    question: "Increase 185 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 185$ and then add on, or Find 135% of 185, $1.35 \\times 185$"
    answer: 249.75
-
    question: "Increase 117 by 10%"
    solution: "Find 10% $0.1 \\times 117$ and then add on, or Find 110% of 117, $1.1 \\times 117$"
    answer: 128.7
-
    question: "Increase 109 by 10%"
    solution: "Find 10% $0.1 \\times 109$ and then add on, or Find 110% of 109, $1.1 \\times 109$"
    answer: 119.9
-
    question: "Decrease 148 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 148$ and then subtract, or Find 70% of 148, $0.7 \\times 148$"
    answer: 103.6
-
    question: "Decrease 141 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 141$ and then subtract, or Find 60% of 141, $0.6 \\times 141$"
    answer: 84.6
-
    question: "Decrease 141 by 45%"
    solution: "Find 45% $0.45 \\times 141$ and then subtract, or Find 55% of 141, $0.55 \\times 141$"
    answer: 77.55
-
    question: "Decrease 241 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 241$ and then subtract, or Find 95% of 241, $0.95 \\times 241$"
    answer: 228.95
-
    question: "Decrease 74 by 15%"
    solution: "Find 15% $0.15 \\times 74$ and then subtract, or Find 85% of 74, $0.85 \\times 74$"
    answer: 62.9
-
    question: "Decrease 16 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 16$ and then subtract, or Find 65% of 16, $0.65 \\times 16$"
    answer: 10.4
-
    question: "Decrease 108 by 45%"
    solution: "Find 45% $0.45 \\times 108$ and then subtract, or Find 55% of 108, $0.55 \\times 108$"
    answer: 59.4
-
    question: "Decrease 126 by 20%"
    solution: "Find 20% $0.2 \\times 126$ and then subtract, or Find 80% of 126, $0.8 \\times 126$"
    answer: 100.8
-
    question: "Decrease 232 by 90%"
    solution: "Find 90% $0.9 \\times 232$ and then subtract, or Find 10% of 232, $0.1 \\times 232$"
    answer: 23.2
-
    question: "Decrease 90 by 85%"
    solution: "Find 85% $0.85 \\times 90$ and then subtract, or Find 15% of 90, $0.15 \\times 90$"
    answer: 13.5
-
    question: "Decrease 97 by 75%"
    solution: "Find 75% $0.75 \\times 97$ and then subtract, or Find 25% of 97, $0.25 \\times 97$"
    answer: 24.25
-
    question: "Decrease 91 by 45%"
    solution: "Find 45% $0.45 \\times 91$ and then subtract, or Find 55% of 91, $0.55 \\times 91$"
    answer: 50.05
-
    question: "Decrease 244 by 10%"
    solution: "Find 10% $0.1 \\times 244$ and then subtract, or Find 90% of 244, $0.9 \\times 244$"
    answer: 219.6
-
    question: "Decrease 238 by 60%"
    solution: "Find 60% $0.6 \\times 238$ and then subtract, or Find 40% of 238, $0.4 \\times 238$"
    answer: 95.2
-
    question: "Decrease 102 by 85%"
    solution: "Find 85% $0.85 \\times 102$ and then subtract, or Find 15% of 102, $0.15 \\times 102$"
    answer: 15.3
-
    question: "Decrease 115 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 115$ and then subtract, or Find 60% of 115, $0.6 \\times 115$"
    answer: 69
-
    question: "Decrease 19 by 50%"
    solution: "Find 50% $0.5 \\times 19$ and then subtract, or Find 50% of 19, $0.5 \\times 19$"
    answer: 9.5
-
    question: "Decrease 71 by 50%"
    solution: "Find 50% $0.5 \\times 71$ and then subtract, or Find 50% of 71, $0.5 \\times 71$"
    answer: 35.5
-
    question: "Decrease 123 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 123$ and then subtract, or Find 20% of 123, $0.2 \\times 123$"
    answer: 24.6
-
    question: "Decrease 53 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 53$ and then subtract, or Find 95% of 53, $0.95 \\times 53$"
    answer: 50.35
-
    question: "Decrease 100 by 15%"
    solution: "Find 15% $0.15 \\times 100$ and then subtract, or Find 85% of 100, $0.85 \\times 100$"
    answer: 85
-
    question: "Decrease 201 by 70%"
    solution: "Find 70% $0.7 \\times 201$ and then subtract, or Find 30% of 201, $0.3 \\times 201$"
    answer: 60.3
-
    question: "Decrease 36 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 36$ and then subtract, or Find 70% of 36, $0.7 \\times 36$"
    answer: 25.2
-
    question: "Decrease 83 by 50%"
    solution: "Find 50% $0.5 \\times 83$ and then subtract, or Find 50% of 83, $0.5 \\times 83$"
    answer: 41.5
-
    question: "Decrease 36 by 65%"
    solution: "Find 65% $0.65 \\times 36$ and then subtract, or Find 35% of 36, $0.35 \\times 36$"
    answer: 12.6
-
    question: "Decrease 64 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 64$ and then subtract, or Find 70% of 64, $0.7 \\times 64$"
    answer: 44.8
-
    question: "Decrease 72 by 65%"
    solution: "Find 65% $0.65 \\times 72$ and then subtract, or Find 35% of 72, $0.35 \\times 72$"
    answer: 25.2
-
    question: "Decrease 179 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 179$ and then subtract, or Find 65% of 179, $0.65 \\times 179$"
    answer: 116.35
-
    question: "Decrease 89 by 60%"
    solution: "Find 60% $0.6 \\times 89$ and then subtract, or Find 40% of 89, $0.4 \\times 89$"
    answer: 35.6
-
    question: "Decrease 169 by 60%"
    solution: "Find 60% $0.6 \\times 169$ and then subtract, or Find 40% of 169, $0.4 \\times 169$"
    answer: 67.6
-
    question: "Decrease 66 by 85%"
    solution: "Find 85% $0.85 \\times 66$ and then subtract, or Find 15% of 66, $0.15 \\times 66$"
    answer: 9.9
-
    question: "Decrease 240 by 25%"
    solution: "Find 25% $0.25 \\times 240$ and then subtract, or Find 75% of 240, $0.75 \\times 240$"
    answer: 180
-
    question: "Decrease 25 by 75%"
    solution: "Find 75% $0.75 \\times 25$ and then subtract, or Find 25% of 25, $0.25 \\times 25$"
    answer: 6.25
-
    question: "Decrease 222 by 50%"
    solution: "Find 50% $0.5 \\times 222$ and then subtract, or Find 50% of 222, $0.5 \\times 222$"
    answer: 111
-
    question: "Decrease 161 by 85%"
    solution: "Find 85% $0.85 \\times 161$ and then subtract, or Find 15% of 161, $0.15 \\times 161$"
    answer: 24.15
-
    question: "Decrease 81 by 65%"
    solution: "Find 65% $0.65 \\times 81$ and then subtract, or Find 35% of 81, $0.35 \\times 81$"
    answer: 28.35
-
    question: "Decrease 127 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 127$ and then subtract, or Find 60% of 127, $0.6 \\times 127$"
    answer: 76.2
-
    question: "Decrease 247 by 15%"
    solution: "Find 15% $0.15 \\times 247$ and then subtract, or Find 85% of 247, $0.85 \\times 247$"
    answer: 209.95
-
    question: "Decrease 152 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 152$ and then subtract, or Find 20% of 152, $0.2 \\times 152$"
    answer: 30.4
-
    question: "Decrease 116 by 40%"
    solution: "Find 40% $0.4 \\times 116$ and then subtract, or Find 60% of 116, $0.6 \\times 116$"
    answer: 69.6
-
    question: "Decrease 72 by 20%"
    solution: "Find 20% $0.2 \\times 72$ and then subtract, or Find 80% of 72, $0.8 \\times 72$"
    answer: 57.6
-
    question: "Decrease 79 by 45%"
    solution: "Find 45% $0.45 \\times 79$ and then subtract, or Find 55% of 79, $0.55 \\times 79$"
    answer: 43.45
-
    question: "Decrease 198 by 5%"
    solution: "Find 5% $0.05 \\times 198$ and then subtract, or Find 95% of 198, $0.95 \\times 198$"
    answer: 188.1
-
    question: "Decrease 229 by 70%"
    solution: "Find 70% $0.7 \\times 229$ and then subtract, or Find 30% of 229, $0.3 \\times 229$"
    answer: 68.7
-
    question: "Decrease 226 by 50%"
    solution: "Find 50% $0.5 \\times 226$ and then subtract, or Find 50% of 226, $0.5 \\times 226$"
    answer: 113
-
    question: "Decrease 53 by 90%"
    solution: "Find 90% $0.9 \\times 53$ and then subtract, or Find 10% of 53, $0.1 \\times 53$"
    answer: 5.3
-
    question: "Decrease 136 by 80%"
    solution: "Find 80% $0.8 \\times 136$ and then subtract, or Find 20% of 136, $0.2 \\times 136$"
    answer: 27.2
-
    question: "Decrease 68 by 30%"
    solution: "Find 30% $0.3 \\times 68$ and then subtract, or Find 70% of 68, $0.7 \\times 68$"
    answer: 47.6
-
    question: "Decrease 238 by 20%"
    solution: "Find 20% $0.2 \\times 238$ and then subtract, or Find 80% of 238, $0.8 \\times 238$"
    answer: 190.4
-
    question: "Decrease 107 by 35%"
    solution: "Find 35% $0.35 \\times 107$ and then subtract, or Find 65% of 107, $0.65 \\times 107$"
    answer: 69.55
